What?
What do you want?
Vicenta, have you seen how this remote control is?
It's in the living room.
No, honey, it's full of bites.
I'm teaching Valentina to be a traitor.
Honey, when you learn, it's no longer working.
What do you want for breakfast tomorrow?
Come on, I don't want to go, it's a trip of jewelry.
Hey, I bought the ticket, it cost me 6 euros.
Well, look, it's on sale at the bus door.
It's going to be full of bites.
I don't want to walk 200 kilometers
so I can be released in the field like Geiza and Vicenta.
It's going to be fun. There's going to be a cape.
A cape?
These delinquents don't know what to do to get rid of the old ones.
What's this idiot going to do? How are you going to come?
Come on, well, I'm going, but shut up.
And tell this dog not to follow me.
And don't follow me, Valentin, it's fine.
Ma'am, all I'm telling you is that I don't need the rope.
I need it.
You have a dryer, I see it from here.
If you don't see it...
Are you calling me a
I'm going to go.
Yes, Emilio.
Don't worry about me.
This portal is mine and I control it.
If I say everybody can clean their feet,
they're clean and that's it.
How are you?
Did you do anything to him?
He's a smart guy.
He's very good.
Don't look at him, he's useless.
I like that guy.
He's got something.
He's a boyfriend and lives with him.
Yeah?
Every time you see a handsome guy he's gay.
Sadly, yeah.
Come on, come on in.
I'm going up the stairs, it's good for the ass.
Wait, I'm coming with you.
Now you leave the elevator door open,
so you don't have to fix it.
Oh...
WHISTLING
Hello.
What, renting a movie?
No, I'm taking time off
to get home late and annoy my father.
Oh, very well.
How's your girlfriend?
What?
My girlfriend?
Good, very good.
I don't see you mature enough to maintain a stable relationship.
Oh, no? No.
If you commit, you'll regret it.
But it'll be too late.
You'll have wasted the best years of your life
and you'll be the typical family father,
trapped in the routine.
How sad, right?
I'll tell you.
Lulu's age.
What?
Lulu, no.
I'm here with the hive.
I'm leaving, it's 1.20.
We'll keep talking, right?
How's the president's daughter?
Hey, I have a girlfriend.
Me too.
Hello.
Well, honey, is the egg ready?
She's thinking about it.
No, I've already chosen.
Of course.
Well, I'll wait for you at home.
Of course, this one's also very good.
Yeah, but she has a boyfriend.
And me?
Here, here, here, no one lives,
here no, here no.
Every day is like this,
I couldn't imagine it when I came here,
I was just looking for something to eat.
Every day is like this, I couldn't imagine it when I came here,
Here, here, here, no one lives,
here no, here no.
Every day is like this, I couldn't imagine it when I came here,
I was just looking for something to eat.
The house on the start of Rumba,
I can't find the doorman,
the neighbors watch and listen to me,
I can't stand it in this place,
they put me in a glass,
where do we enter this staircase?
Here, here, here, no one lives,
here no, here no.
here no.
education
and
myself
good
Don't worry, I'll paint it later.
Benito, the radiator is down there.
And put the plastics on.
Where are you going to start?
First, that wall outside.
We take off the paint, paint that wall, lift the floor and get into the kitchen.
How long will it take?
Faster than fast.
I like it that way.
Antonio, look, sorry, he's Roberto.
Come on, boy, in ten days you'll be home.
Can we talk for a moment?
Hey, Antonio, don't forget about the moldings.
Yes, yes, you're asked.
What is this?
Antonio, the captain.
What are these people doing here? What's going on?
Reform?
Reform.
But don't you remember I told you?
They are from my father's construction, they have made a hole for us.
You know how lucky we are.
Are you sure we've talked about this?
Sure, you never listen to me when I talk to you.
Well, I'm leaving.
Anything you need, ask Roberto.
Wait, I'll go with you.
I have to go to the warehouse for a material.
I'll leave you with that, I'll hit you.
Well, honey, goodbye.
Okay, then I'll call you, you'll tell me.
Good luck.
Well, do you know what you have to do?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, until what time are you going to be more or less?
You speak Spanish, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
This is going to be fun.
Come on, honey, breakfast, we're getting late.
Natalia, we're leaving.
And dad, get out of the bathroom.
I'm going.
But, honey, take those kids away, you're going to school.
You, we're not going.
We're not going.
What childhood are you giving me, among all?
Shut up, shut up.
Are you listening?
Those are works.
Juan, Juan, works, works.
Yes, yes, I'm listening, they're the new ones.
These guys up there have started throwing tabics.
Well, they haven't warned me.
Neither have I, what a shame.
When you do your homework, you don't warn anyone either.
Of course, because I'm the president.
I'm going to talk to them right now.
Take the papers, honey.
I can't, Juan, because I have an appointment with the gynecologist.
Juan.
No, no, there's no hurry, I have an exam.
And me?
Come on, don't eat anymore.
Is it over?
Mom, you're scratching me.
I'm going to scratch you, well scratched.
How are you, Natalia, please help me.
Lucia.
Lucia, listen to me.
Look, this is the third message I leave you, call me.
I think the guys have brought this, your parents are doing what they want.
A kiss.
But hey, what is this?
According to article 17 of the horizontal property law, paragraph 5,
the works must be notified to the president of the community at least a week before the start.
I am the president of the community and I knew nothing.
I didn't know, I live here, you'll see.
Well, at least you'll have a permit to work at the city hall, right?
Green paper, the copy.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, what?
We don't have it.
The one who has it is in my girlfriend's house and is working and doesn't answer the phone.
Well, you have to stop the work until this is cleared.
Come on, stop working.
Not kick-ass.
Stop working.
Hey, hey.
Nothing, nothing, don't bother, if they don't speak Spanish.
Pick, pick-stop.
No picking.
Nothing, but if I have tried, they don't speak English either.
Hey, I'm telling you, don't kick-ass.
Well, you have to speak languages.
Hey.
It's over.
Finished.
Now to house.
Holidays.
Ok?
Come on.
Go, go.
Go.
Do you see how they understand me?
That's how you miss the pronunciation, I'm sure.
What a mess.
Pum-ta-ta-pum-ta-pum-ta-ta.
Here there is no one alive, Ole.
Man, the angels of Charlie.
How was the tour?
Very well.
They have taken us on a bus, they have taken us on a trip, they have given us a little bite and they have tried to sell us an express pot.
Beautiful day.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Have you watched the two gulfs up there?
I haven't seen them all day today, Mrs. Concha.
I'm going to see what they're doing.
Very well.
You should have seen Toreando in the capea.
It's a good thing I took the vaquilla off her, tell me right away, or she'll kill her.
Come on.
It's just been a stir.
Oh, come on, hurry up.
As if we had something to do.
Come on, you three are going pretty, with the cap.
Oh, mother, what a day I have, my God, what a tiredness.
I have a desire to take off my shoes.
Tonight I'm going to put on some heels.
Vicenta, I opened the door for you.
I do not.
What do you mean you do not?
If you do not, I leave the door open.
Thieves have entered.
Oh, my God, they've entered our house.
But what happened?
They have forced us to the door, look.
Oh, what gentleness is loose.
God, I said there were no excursions here, there were no excursions here.
Well, go guard dog.
But how are you?
How are you?
Commercial, computer, carpenter, commercial.
What are you doing looking for work?
No, I'm looking at the shelves, let's see if my ex appears.
How's the casting?
I have not been caught.
But I have found Fernando again on the portal.
Oh, very nice.
We did not arrive at the end of the month and you thinking about the neighbor.
Oh, I'm confused.
It's the first time that a guy I like does not listen to me.
You end up getting used to it.
I'll have to take the initiative.
What a good love.
Look, Ali, I tell you because I'm your friend.
You're going to get a lot of trouble.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I have come up with a super original idea to talk to Fernando.
Which?
Hello.
Do you have salt?
Yes, of course, a moment.
It's super original.
Alicia is pathetic, come on.
Whatever you want, but it works.
You'll see how to get a girl.
Take it.
And be careful with the salt, which retains a lot of liquids.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It works.
What I have not been very clear is what time you have been.
Well, yes, they have forced the door.
I do not know why, but they have forced the door.
Well, at least they have not taken anything.
I think they have seen Valentí and he was scared.
That must be.
And you have not seen anyone strange?
No, apart from you, no.
That's what they wanted, if we have nothing.
Well, you have been lucky not to be at home, that if you arrive to be,
the same violates that kill you both.
I do not know how you can live quietly in a first.
The day less thought, they enter through the window and if not, in time.
I live in a second and also my son is.
If not, it's been a long time since I had put an alarm.
And what does an alarm cost?
Hello, honey.
How have they left this like this?
Finally someone who speaks my language.
What happened? They have not done anything.
The president of the community has arrived
and they are standing in no matter what paragraph, no matter what article,
they have stopped the works.
What has he done?
Hello, Lucia.
But who do you think you are to stop me the works?
I am the president of the community.
No, you have no right to get into my house to think about anything.
I do not know if you know that to make reforms at home
you need a permit to work in the town hall.
Oh yeah? And what is that?
At first glance it seems a permit to work in the town hall.
And now what? Are you going to pay me the delay?
Man, I do not think it's worth it.
I'm going to pay you the delay.
What is that scandal? What voices are those?
Nothing, Doña Concha, nothing.
Oh, they are not hours.
What? And what are you looking at?
Juan, do not let yourself be, do not let yourself be.
Marisa, this is the house of the president of the community.
I do not know what you are doing here.
I am going to tell you everything.
Marisa, are you asleep?
Nooo.
Hey, what are we going to do if they come back?
Who are they?
The ones who have broken the door.
And who tells you that they are going to come back if they did not take anything?
Of course, because maybe they are looking for us.
Of course, they have seen us on the cover of the interview and they have been caught.
I'm serious.
Look, sleep and leave me alone.
What is that noise?
Valentín, look, look, look.
Today I better sleep with my teeth on, I will not have to bite someone.
But who can get up to work at eight in the morning apart from Iñaki Capilondo?
Oh, sorry, if I say it for these, sorry, Fernando, a kiss, give me a kiss.
Oh, be careful, let's see if you go down and wash my sheets.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, they have already finished with the peak.
Look, look, look.
Sorry.
Go.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, not there.
Not there, elevator, the elevator is for people.
The bags on the stairs and without stain, come on, let's go.
Look how he is putting me, but this guy is stupid.
Kid.
The bag outside, damn it, stay there.
The bag outside, on the stairs, I'm telling you.
Throw it on the stairs.
Wait, I'm going to shit myself.
Over here, damn it, throw it over here, throw it over there.
That guy is frozen, this guy, I have to take it out.
The mother fucker.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Mother fucker.
Well, yes.
Come on.
You can't come and stop the works, you can't.
I've tried it, but you can't.
This is unbearable, man.
My hair is falling off because of the stress.
Everything is made of churrasco.
Well, I clean, but they are very fat.
But hey, they don't have to warn us.
Well, nobody has come here to tell us anything.
Because this lady does her job very badly.
Hey, my husband does a lot, huh?
Well, we'll have to see the accounts.
You can't stand it, it's seven and they're still here.
According to the law, they can be working until nine at night.
But it starts at eight and they're there all day long,
stinging.
Well, it's terrible to sting for three hours.
Well, a little joke to relax us.
How funny.
Well, they have entered our house to steal from us because
the portal is open all day.
And everything is made of churrasco.
Yes, it feels nice, we've heard it before.
Well, I don't know what the solution is, but something has to be done.
I know it's uncomfortable for everyone, for me the first one.
But they have promised me that they will finish right away.
Hey, they are very short.
Yes, yes, yes.
He doesn't speak Spanish, huh?
Go, president.
Alicia, you know that stealing cards is a crime.
If I'm going to return it,
then go down to his house and tell him that they have
been wrong in the field of our house.
It's worse than the sun, it's going over you for a moment.
Oh, I'm going to kill you. Get her out, get her out.
Come on, let's go.
I think this is our safe.
And the letter?
Look, my name.
See? That's why I didn't open the key.
If it's not our safe.
If you're clumsy, come on.
But what are you doing?
I don't know.
What are you going to know if you don't know anything?
Ladies,
congratulations on your choice.
This alarm system consists of three motion sensors,
located one in room two, kitchen, three, bedroom.
Now you have to enter a four-digit secret code
that under no concept should tell anyone.
Which one do we put?
The one with the credit card 4547.
Shut up, put the one with the money, then you tell me.
Look over there.
That's it.
I repeat, you must not tell anyone.
And now I will explain its operation.
It is very simple.
To activate the alarm system in the entire house,
press a secret key or secret code
then press the enter key on the lower right.
If you only unlock a specific area,
press the bypass key
kept on your left top right.
And the area number should be disabled.
One for the room, two for the kitchen, three for the bedroom.
Then hold the shift key,
located on the upper right.
Then for five seconds to close the red button
on the bottom left of the control panel.
Then this time only press the enter key.
That's it.
Do you understand?
Congratulations.
Are you with Fides again?
How come all the neighbours are going with me?
I don't understand.
What fault do I have that the upper ones start working?
All I'm saying is that with that attitude
you're going to put the whole neighbourhood on top of you.
What attitude?
Let's see. Who's in charge here?
You.
No, in the community.
Ah, me.
Me.
Well, and you, huh?
I'm sure that these people up here are doing something illegal.
Weren't they throwing a wall?
Yes.
Well, it's a load.
How do you know?
And what else does it matter how you know it or not?
You say it's a load.
Of course.
And then they need an architect to sign the project.
Well, there it is.
I'm convinced that she wants to change the windows.
And they want to close the terrace.
Alteration of common elements.
Tomorrow you go up and you look at what they're doing.
Those people still haven't found out who we are.
But they will.
Marisa.
You've fallen asleep.
No, I'm watching TV.
Come on, let's go to bed, we have to set the alarm.
Come on, damn it.
Let's see how this is.
Code.
Zone.
Enter.
And now we have ten seconds to leave the living room.
Come on, run to the bedroom.
Come on, let's go.
But without pushing.
Oh, well, all right.
Come on.
My little glass of milk.
Leave it, there's no time.
No, no, there's still time.
Otherwise I won't sleep.
No, run, run.
Yes, yes.
Oh.
Someone is calling.
You're the one who's been calling.
I have it, I said.
This is the condom.
They also install the drama without my permission.
Now, for God's sake, the phone.
Turn off that, you're going to be on TV.
Who is it now?
Emilio.
Yes, tell me.
What is that?
What is it?
The scandal that is down there.
Those are the girls, Mr. Juan, who have set an alarm.
Come on, go up and see what happens.
Yes, yes, now I'm going, Mr. Juan, yes, now I'm going.
You go up with the girls.
I'm going to the bathroom.
You go up with your sister, the one from Alcalá de Nares,
you asshole.
Call me at 2 in the morning, it's going to be...
It's going to be abnormal, man.
The paper, take the paper, take the paper.
Fuck, but what happened?
It's an alarm.
I'm going to see what happens.
No, no, don't go.
Don't worry, nothing is going to happen to me.
You go to sleep.
But if I can't.
Put the code in, please.
I've already put it in, but I don't know where I've touched.
I'll ask for help.
No, let it go, let it go, let it go, let it go.
They're sleeping.
But how are they going to sleep?
They seem to be bombing us.
Are you all right?
Yes, I don't know what he's done with the alarm.
Come on, come on, son, do you want to drink something?
Let's see, tell me the code.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a secret, we can't tell anyone.
Ma'am, I'm your neighbor.
Vicenta, for my time, tell us.
But what happened?
Who came in?
This one.
I came to help.
So you set up an alarm and you don't tell me?
What was missing?
Why don't you disconnect it?
Why don't you want to tell me the code?
Vicenta, tell us, then change it and that's it.
No, I know this code very well because it's my date of birth.
And how old are you?
65 years old, why?
Oh, how relieved.
How did you do it?
Well, come on, it's fine, let's all go to bed.
Good night.
What security.
Security?
I don't know anyone.
Come on, let's go to bed.
Let's go to bed.
Let's see, is it clear?
Yes, yes, yes.
I touched my forehead like this.
I say my phrase.
But what is your phrase?
I got a lot of dirt in the building.
But what, sir, I've pissed you off as if you were upset.
No, it's just that it bothers me.
Well, let's go, let's go.
Come on.
I touch my forehead and what do you say?
I got a lot of dirt in the building.
Well, better, better, come on, let's keep rehearsing.
I touch my forehead and you say?
I got a lot of dirt in the building.
There, there, that's it.
Come on, sir, I put on a little teacup to the theater.
And why did you leave it?
Because my mother said this was from Maritita.
Listen to me, don't keep painting, please.
This color doesn't like my girlfriend.
This color is horrible.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, but keep painting.
In addition, you are destroying the park,
put a little plastic, come on.
Hello.
Man, Juan Cuesta, president of the community.
Indeed, I have to tell you that we have detected certain irregularities in this way
and the wish of the entire community is that the works end immediately.
I agree.
Now you tell them, please.
You are causing many problems.
And I get very dirty in the difficult.
You're right, Emilio.
But hey, are you here again?
What do you want?
Don't let me in.
I was telling your boyfriend that you have thrown a load wall.
A load wall, a load wall, what does it say?
And for that you need a project and the signature of an architect.
Well, Roberto is an architect.
Eh?
Ah, no, eh, well, well, well, well,
to what I was going to ...
And I got very dirty in the building.
Oh, come on, what's up with the building editors?
They're going to clean it up when they're done.
Oh, and you're also going to change the windows.
Well, if we're going to change the windows, what happens?
Well, it's an alteration of common elements.
Any neighbor could be bothered by it and report you.
Are you threatening us?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Better, because if not, I'm going to report the second B for the parabolic antenna,
the first B for the air conditioning
and the first A for hanging the pots off the balcony
and the community,
because the extinguishers have not passed the last five reviews
and that elevator has not a single security measure.
Well, I don't think it's going to be like that either.
Now that we're talking about it ...
And the building is very dirty.
You want to shut up already, Emilio?
Well, I have a document for the front.
And this man is living in a common area
that according to the plans of the building is a garbage room.
That I live in a garbage room?
Come on, call the city hall, do an inspection
and tomorrow this man is in the street.
Mr. Juan, they want to throw me out.
Hey, honey, I don't think that's for ...
No, no, no, no.
If we're going to talk things, we're going to talk things.
Okay.
In view of your attitude, I have no choice
but to call an extraordinary neighborhood meeting.
Very well.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Hey, don't throw me away, please.
It will be a garbage room, but I have taken care of it, damn it.
Emilio!
Coming, coming.
A little bit of human warmth, huh?
Nasty.
Well, why do you let them paint the wall in that color?
What did I say?
There it is.
But what happened? What happened?
What happened?
That a new neighbor is going to be set up,
they are going to report us to everyone.
And to us, why?
To you two for the geraniums that you have hung on the balcony.
See, I told you not to take them from the park.
If no one saw me?
No, no, if you have hung them outside
and that is prohibited, why does that fall?
A pot or whatever falls on the head and it opens.
But if you can't see inside.
And this one, the parabolic, they are going to take it away.
See?
I already told you that to put it you had to ask for permission.
But they want to throw me out of the goal
because they say this is a garbage room.
But that doesn't matter to anyone.
And to you two, the air.
What?
Yes, yes, the air is air-conditioned.
You have it under the window
and that is terminally prohibited.
Let's see, who wants to take it away from us?
The new neighbors.
Well, let them buy one.
But let's see, what have we done
so that they want to report us to everyone?
The president of the community
who has put himself on the edge
and wants to stop the work.
And then she has rebounded
and these pijas when they rebound,
apparently they are.
Well, I don't take my generals away.
If I have to go to jail, I go to jail.
And I with you.
Well, but that's not all.
They say that the building is in ruins,
that they are going to call an inspector
and that they are going to be paying for branches
until Spain wins again Eurovision festival.
How do you see it?
Hey, you lawyer, can that happen?
Winning Eurovision?
It's complicated.
No, man, no.
They report us and we have to keep paying for branches of those.
Well, yes, the truth is,
as they are talking seriously,
they can get us in trouble.
Good afternoon.
Alicia, do you want to explain what I do here?
You make the fool alone.
Hello.
The shirt I've thrown is yours.
Oh.
Hello.
Sorry, we were having the clothes
and Belén has dropped a shirt on your accord.
Yes, I dropped it.
This one, right?
Yes, just.
As I don't know who it is, I'm going to lower it to the goalkeeper.
No, not to the goalkeeper, that it stays.
Well, well.
Well nothing.
One day we could stay four and have a drink.
Yes, yes, come whenever you want.
Tonight?
Tonight.
Tomorrow?
I don't know if ...
Are you coming at 10?
At 10, yes.
In your house.
No, better here, no.
Well, no.
Tell your friend, huh?
To Mauri.
Yes, yes, I'll tell him.
Come on, he's going to be delighted.
What?
But why did you stay with them?
But what did you want me to do?
I couldn't think of any excuse.
Well, there are very good ones.
That you are gay, that you have a boyfriend,
a stable relationship.
But if nothing happens, we stay with her,
we chat for a while, we have a drink and so friendly ...
No, no, no, no, no, with me you count.
I have nothing else to do at this point than to go straight for life.
No, no.
But what happens, that I can't have friends or what?
Yes, if they are lesbians.
What are you laughing at?
Let's see, no, what are you laughing at?
It's that it seems so absurd that it makes me laugh.
Oh yeah?
You know what happens to you?
That you like that.
Don't say that, Mauri.
Yes, and you want to check what it feels like
when one is sleeping with a woman.
I already slept with a woman.
Don't remind me.
Please, it's not necessary.
You know what I'm telling you?
I have to take care of the rabbit.
If you want to throw five years of relationship by the edge,
you throw them, what happens?
You.
We take three.
Do you have anything else?
They have made me very long.
You know what Fernando?
I'm leaving.
Where?
I have no idea, but I'm leaving.
Well, it's me.
Mauri.
Uy, uy, uy, uy, uy, uy, uy, uy, uy, uy, uy.
Honey.
Are you really going to give up on me?
Of course not.
Why?
Because we are not going to get out of here alive.
Calm down, I just wanted to put fear in your body.
Yeah, but you've put it in me.
You should have run your voice
because on the portal
they have dedicated me a few affectionate looks.
Yeah, and what did you want me to do?
It's that guy down there who makes me sick.
Well, I don't know, but at least consult me.
Maybe I don't feel like living in front of all the neighbors.
I have enough with the works.
Okay.
I feel a little tense.
Tense?
No, I haven't cut my veins
because I can't find the knife with the cause.
I also want to relax a little.
Don't get angry.
Let's see, ma'am.
I can't come and disconnect the alarm every time it jumps.
Man, please, I have the children sleeping.
Between this and the works, no one stops here.
We haven't been there this time.
We were in the bedroom, right?
I don't even know where I am.
I have a horrible dream.
So who was it?
Vicenta, if you let the dog loose, the alarm jumps.
And why?
If Valentino is a thief.
No, but he moves.
And that's a motion sensor.
Can't you see how it's not a camera?
And every time you pass in front of it, you greet it.
Hey, Juan, this can't go on like this.
Let's see.
If you don't know how to use the alarm, don't connect it.
What do you mean no?
What if they don't come in?
Nobody has entered since 68.
Well, come on, come on, everyone to sleep.
But my son, I'm not going to sleep.
But look, he's connecting it again.
Of course.
We're going to bed.
Come on, everyone, out, we have 10 seconds.
You come, take the dog.
Come on, Valentin.
Valentin.
Ladies, for God's sake, that alarm.
We have to wake them up.
Oh, what a...
Hello.
We're here.
Sorry for the delay.
It's just that Tasco caught us.
Come in.
What do you have in this bottle of whiskey?
Oh, very good, thank you very much.
I'll serve you others, okay?
I prefer wine.
Sit down.
What a nice house, huh?
Very nice.
With...
I would have gone up to the bike ride.
Mauri has gone up to the neighbors' meeting.
He won't be able to come.
Oh.
But well, nothing happens.
We drink something, the three of us.
Yes, yes, nothing happens.
As soon as I get this feeling of humiliation,
I'm sure I'll have a great time.
You've realized, haven't you?
Yes, pathetic.
It's that I don't care about those I don't like, Alicia.
No, Fernando told Mauri to go so that we can stay alone.
Betty, Betty.
What do you mean, go?
But what do you want, to stay here, with those jetties?
Well, as usual, as soon as you start giving the lot,
I can watch TV.
No, Betty.
Thank you, we always do it like that.
I don't know what comes.
Thank you.
Well, the wine.
Yes.
And some chips or something.
Sure.
Are you all right?
Do you need something?
A ash-tree.
Oh, no, not that, because you can't smoke here.
Fuck, with Europe, you can't smoke
in the neighbors' meetings.
I'm sorry.
We'll start right away.
But take canapés, eat,
they're for eating, not to look at them.
They're great, huh?
Now I'm going back.
What canapés?
What do you mean, mortadela?
Well, it's delicious, huh?
She has put butter and everything.
It's a man.
I'm not hungry.
Well, what tension is there in the environment.
Well, let's see, I've already taken notes.
If an inspection comes and we have to fix
the elevator, the ladder, the paint, the cracks,
the extinguishers and change the boiler,
the boiler costs us about 18,000 euros.
Three million pesos.
Oh, well, isn't it that much between all of us?
No, three million pesos per floor.
Oh, my God, what are you saying?
But how are we going to pay for that?
I prefer that the roof falls and kills us all.
It's the fault of that idiot
of a president that we have.
And what about you?
Don't you say anything?
Yes, I'm leaving.
But how are you going to get there?
Where are you going?
You have to vote.
There's always a trap.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
If you get there now, it's going to seem like you're jealous.
And you're not jealous, Mauri.
Do whatever you want.
It's also my house,
and I can go in and out whenever I want.
Look, it's not that it's too soon.
Look, I'm going to go down.
Besides, killing me, I'm getting home with less.
That lawyer sounds very nice, doesn't he?
At first you think you're going to fix the world.
The world is shit.
I don't have a job.
Neither does he.
I don't even talk to my parents.
Men are all immature.
Hey, Vanessa is going to have to go.
She's not feeling well, she told me before.
Well, well, well.
We'll meet another day.
No, but it's not that bad.
Stay a while, woman.
I'm here.
Now.
Forgive me for being late, but...
I've met my ex-girlfriend and she's given me a number.
What are you saying?
What you hear is that she's been nervous.
She's been trying to cut her veins with the transport hub.
Very unpleasant.
Weren't you at the meeting?
No, no, I wasn't.
We thought you weren't coming anymore.
Well, here I am.
Belén has stopped asking about you.
Well, I asked something.
Don't be shy, woman.
Well, I'm going to get a drink.
You want more ice, right?
I do.
I'm going to put ice on me.
We're all nervous.
Since when do you like whiskey?
Since you like women.
You'll see, you'll see how well we're going to have it.
Have they all arrived?
They're missing the new ones.
They're scared.
Have you seen that all the neighbors support me and they've backed out?
I didn't want to get into this situation.
Paloma, you know what?
Yes.
They've forgotten me.
Yes, honey.
Come on, come on.
To triumph.
Courage.
Oh, my president.
What a great bet.
Good afternoon, welcome everyone.
We're going to start the extraordinary meeting.
The new ones are missing.
Well, but we're enough owners for the vote to be valid.
So let's get started.
Turn off your mobile phone and don't smoke.
To talk, raise your hand.
And to insult, also raise it.
Day's order.
Point first.
Good evening.
Sorry for the delay.
She was so cute.
Continue.
Point first.
Voting to exercise the action of ceasing and formally require the owner of the third A
to stop the annoying and unhealthy and harmful activity that is developing in their home
and that prevents the normal development of coexistence in this community.
Well, we didn't come to talk about the works.
Well, that's what she said.
That we are going to vote everyone to stop the works.
What bad does your husband explain?
He makes a bet so that we don't understand him.
We're starting.
Dear neighbors, as you know,
we have had some new neighbors who have decided to take a step forward to this community.
Without warning anyone,
they have started some reform works that bother us all
and that put the security of the building in danger.
That's a lie.
Please, respect that the president is talking about.
I'm not going to tell you in person.
I tell you that if we vote in favor of the separation of the works,
the works are separated.
Or that, or we go to court.
So let's vote.
Emilio, I'm going to count the votes.
Yes, Mr. President.
Votes in favor of the separation of the work.
One.
Well, let's see, I don't think you've understood me well.
I said those who are in favor,
in favor,
of the separation of the works,
raise your hand.
One, one.
I see it.
Well, you've all complained, no one is going to raise their hand.
Man, Vicenta, thank you.
Two votes in favor.
No, no, where is the bathroom?
The bathroom is there, to the right.
It's possible, you're in a hurry.
Thank you.
Well, let's see, votes against.
I have two votes, I remember.
One, two, three, all.
Well, I don't understand anything.
Can you know what's going on here?
Poor things, they don't bother so much either.
I'm not used to the noise.
I'm not, but in the parabolic no one touches it.
So you sold yourself, you gave in to blackmail and threaten that woman.
What a shame, it's outrageous.
What is outrageous is that our works are so important to her.
When I find it much more serious the state of the building or the poor management of the community.
Yes, that's very good, but it sounds like demagogy, because it doesn't appear in the order of the day.
The girl is right, the stairs are so easy, the other day I almost killed myself.
And the phone is killing me.
They told us that in the electrical installation we had to change it.
If the day was less thought out, the building would have burned down and we would all die carbonized.
If they are going to have to identify us by the teeth.
This one doesn't have.
Well, let's see, we've already talked about that and it's true that we have to do things, but now there is no money.
Where is it?
In the new car that they have bought.
But hey, lady.
One moment, are you doubting my honesty?
I think so.
You are doubting, you are doubting.
Do you think that a manager is going to be in charge, like everyone else?
Maybe you're not doing the maths right.
Chorizo!
In 12 years that I have been president, I had never heard anything like it.
12 years.
But the president is elected every year.
My husband is the only one who introduces himself every year as a volunteer.
Well, I offer myself as a volunteer.
Maybe what the community needs is a change.
I'm not going to resign.
I sincerely believe that my work has been ...
Go ahead, Mr. Cuesta, go ahead.
But how are we going to vote for this girl if we don't know her at all?
Well, she can fix herself on the stairs, I vote for you.
Well, me too, provided I leave my parabolic where it is.
No, but what you have to do is put one for all in the attic, which is cheaper.
And I call the company and my father paints the building for us for half the price.
Order, order, the assembly is suspended.
Why don't we start voting for the girl?
Because the order of the day is not figured out, now.
Order, order, the assembly is suspended.
There are no requests and no questions.
Everyone, go away.
You're done with the chorizo.
Don't worry about anything, Juan, you don't worry about anything.
Well, has it been good, Mr. President?
Here there is no one alive, here there is no one alive, no.
The problem with Fernando with women is that he is very shy, you know, very insecure.
He doesn't know what he wants, right?
Can we stop talking about me, please?
No, I feel the same way, but it's because I haven't found the man of my life yet.
Look, he's looking for him, huh?
He does it every day.
No, but Fernando doesn't give him any eggs.
I mean, he hears the word commitment and runs away.
And the man, I'm afraid he's going to end up very lonely.
Are you with someone now?
There is something.
Yes, there is something.
What we don't know is what it's going to last.
Yes, because he's starting to make me feel a little uncomfortable.
Oh, those are the worst.
They always leave Belén for that.
I'm going to put on a glass, if I have my hands busy.
Fernando, if you feel uncomfortable, it's best you leave it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Sorry, that's not so easy to leave, hey, let her go, let her go.
No, she's a great girl, no.
You tell me what you want, nothing more.
Yes, but Mauri, I don't think she's interested in my personal life.
Oh yes, yes, we are interested, of course.
Well, at this point, I have no choice but to tell you ...
that we have run out of ice.
We have at home.
Is it because of the ice?
The thing is, it's a little late, I have to go to work tomorrow.
I'm going to work, I'm going to work.
If you have ice, just start.
Come on, come on, if you just start ...
Well.
That music.
What?
It's my house.
Let's go up the elevator.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why are we going up through the ice?
We asked these girls, they have everything.
No, man, it's past 12.
But who will be at this hour?
Be careful with the tear.
Come on, come on, come on.
See? I dial the numbers and see if it stops.
That man has written it wrong.
Leave me alone.
Now, to bed.
You'll see how I broke it.
It seems to be taking too long.
Well, yes.
You don't know one thing.
Look, look, Alicia.
I had a great time, you seem like a great girl.
But I don't want anything now.
I'm going through a bit of a personal stage.
Complicated.
I think it would be best if we were just friends.
No, I was going to tell you that I'm going out in this magazine.
Announcing that I'm going to be a friend.
Announcing Muesli bars.
Those energy bars?
Yes.
They are very rich.
I don't like them.
Hey, I'm going to go upstairs.
You want to go to bed.
Yes.
Well, that ...
Nothing, I've had a great time.
That when you want, we can see each other again.
Yeah, you told me before.
Well.
Surprise.
We bring a bottle of tequila and the best of George and Dan.
I'm sorry, I haven't had time to hide it.
The little chiringuito.
Well, I'm going to sleep.
Don't make too much noise, please.
Well, I'm leaving too, I'm very tired.
But what is this? The Muervo route?
It's the first time he's going to sleep before me.
But we have to celebrate it.
And so much.
The little chiringuito.
No, but we ask for it in the drawer.
No, Mauri, Mauri.
What's wrong with dad?
Nothing, honey, he's disgusted.
He's had a bad day.
Why don't we finish him off so he doesn't keep suffering?
Don't say nonsense. Come on, to bed.
Hala, go back to bed.
Come on, both of you.
Juan.
Do you need something?
I've done the ridiculous.
Come on, let's go to bed.
They've lost respect for me, Paloma.
What? No.
If here, except for your children, everyone respects you a lot.
I like to be president.
But you're going to keep being.
Yes, how?
Well, I'll take care of it, don't worry.
Well, what are you going to do?
Well, you don't know what I'm capable of doing for love.
You love me, right, Paloma?
Of course I love you, you're the man of my life.
And I adore you and I wish you.
And you don't know the things I've thought about to keep being president.
I'm going to bed.
Well, I liked that alarm.
I felt safe.
Well, from now on, if you want to feel safe,
you put a compress with wings.
What if the thieves come in?
Well, let them kill us, but in silence.
Hey, I was reading.
Can I come in?
Oh, no, I was reading this, you know.
Belén, I'm caught.
I'm caught.
Look, tomorrow we go out there,
you call another kid and that's it, you forget.
Easy.
At the same time, I shouldn't have kissed him.
You kissed him?
And, and has he answered you?
Not yet.
Oh, girl.
I think it's a matter of giving him time.
Yes, I think so, it's going to be time, that's what...
Yes, it's going to be that, huh.
Well, come on, see you tomorrow, huh.
What a smile you have.
It's cuter.
How cute you are.
Yes.
You like yourself, huh.
Hey, how about at the meeting? What happened?
What happened?
That they wanted to make me president.
Of course, as you can see, I have coconut.
And what did you tell them?
What am I going to tell them?
If you don't pay a cent.
Hey, what am I going to tell you?
I don't know.
Well, I don't know, let's watch a movie.
First you have to be a partner, I'm closing, Emilio.
But what kind of video club is this?
All the empty boxes are empty, this is a mess.
I have the tapes there, so they don't steal them.
This is a cover to sell the
I don't know, I don't know.