heels
The Disaster
Okay, half an hour left, and I'm going to grab something to drink.
Emilio.
How are you, Mrs. Marisa?
Very good.
Hey, the TV's starting to look bad. Why don't you go up to see what's going on with the antenna?
Yeah, I'm going up now, beautiful.
You're not going to the party, Natalia.
Okay, I won't talk to you.
But this girl can hear me.
Help me with the bags.
I'm going, I'm going.
Good afternoon.
Emilio!
The elevator doesn't work!
Yes, it does. The door is open.
Valentín, no. Here, no.
Again, you always see the dog and the door.
Well, I'm not leaving.
Emilio, clean that up.
I'm going.
Hey, the ads in the buckets.
Come on.
Jose Miguel, don't play with the ball.
The bags, the bags.
Tomorrow at eight, the counters will come.
I get in at nine.
You'll have to get up earlier.
And you clean your feet.
What's wrong with you, Polimpia?
You should have studied.
You could have closed the door.
For one thing you have to do.
Hey, you, the street in the Philippines.
I don't know, buy yourself a map.
What the fuck.
Hey, this doesn't go up.
What do you mean it works?
There's no one alive here.
Here, here, here, there's no one alive.
Here, no, here, no.
Every day is like this.
I couldn't imagine it when I came here.
I was just looking for something to eat.
I wake up every day in the middle of a hurricane.
Here, here, here, there's no one alive.
Here, no, here, no.
The house under me collapses.
I can't find the doorman.
The neighbors watch me and listen.
I can't stand it in this place.
They put me in a cocktail bar.
A earthquake and a volcano.
And behind this staircase.
Here, here, here, there's no one alive.
Here, no, here, no.
Alicia, dinner's ready.
Sorry?
I made panache with vegetables and chicken.
What's wrong? Don't you like it?
I can make you a tortilla.
No, I'm excited. It's the first time I see this table.
Is the tablecloth ours?
No, I bought it this morning.
Hey, don't you have a brother around?
Yes, but he's married.
Here comes the man of the house.
Shut up, I can't move.
You and the manager?
No, I've got a bullet in my back.
That's going to be a lumbar.
What?
Don't worry.
Lie down, I'm going to make you a hot water bag.
I'm going to call a friend of mine.
Don't worry.
And this?
Nuria made it.
Don't tell me.
It's perfect.
She won't have a brother for me.
No, she's the only daughter.
I'm so scared.
Why don't you tell me when you're coming?
Try this, please.
We'll have dinner together, but why don't we stay at a restaurant?
Tell Dad to shut up.
It's getting cold. Don't tell me you're deaf.
It's so heavy to see the floor.
It's a normal and ordinary apartment.
It's not a normal and ordinary apartment.
Don't talk about our apartment like that.
Well, we'll stay here.
But on Saturday.
No, we'll stay on Saturday.
Then take a taxi.
Why should I go to the hotel?
Mom, a taxi.
No, don't be fooled.
That's for Japanese.
Come on.
Kiss.
You're having a good time with your parents, aren't you?
Well, I'll hide my pictures and watch the movie.
Mauri.
Don't worry.
I'll tell him.
What?
That we're a couple.
Come on, I'm gay.
What are you going to tell him?
And I'll do whatever you want.
Mauri.
Yes?
The neighbor is watching us.
Let's get separated naturally.
What's up, Tronco?
How are you, ma'am?
Here, learning mathematics.
Nice.
Come on, Concha.
Let's cross the zebra crossing so that the cars get screwed.
No, I'll stay.
Don't you see my face?
Yes, the usual one.
And the night that the upper ones have given me.
Entering and leaving until five in the morning and, on top of that, going up men.
Women will be friends?
Or customers.
Clients? What do you mean?
That are whores.
You'll tell me.
We don't know what they work in.
They enter and leave until the morning.
They dress as they dress.
And, on top of that, they do nothing but go up men.
How do you like to think, Valdez?
Good morning.
This one came yesterday.
He's been here a while and he's leaving.
Relax, woman, it's going to hurt more.
You think in the field.
In the field.
Let me know, let me know.
Well, okay, that's it.
You're better now from back pain.
Yes, I have a sore ass that from the lumbar I can't even walk.
What a pity.
What a beast.
I'm coming.
Well, then tomorrow at the same time, right?
Couldn't it be a little later?
I've been with my wife to take the kids to the movies.
I see.
You've made me dust today.
Come on, don't exaggerate.
Tomorrow at eight o'clock I'm here, okay?
Come on.
See you later.
Goodbye.
See you later, good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
Look at this.
Look how happy he is.
And he's married.
That's why he's coming.
These two have turned my house into a prostitute.
Oh, they've done a work.
I should ask them for a percentage because I love you, madam.
I'm going to see the president right now.
What are they?
The top two girls?
Yes.
I'm the president of the community and I didn't know anything.
And what do you want?
Put a sign next to the phone as if they were dentists.
But Juan, you won't believe anything.
You're the one who's got the girls and you want to throw them out.
I'm going to call the police.
No, no, leave the police.
It's clear that this is a decent building and we're not going to allow unhealthy activities.
But we don't have any proof.
None.
What happens is that you are three bored, the only thing you know how to do is get into people's lives.
Like you.
Oh, you're insulting me, Juan.
Well, the only thing I ask you to do is to be discreet and not to comment on it.
Let's get to know each other.
Dani, uncle, you're going to freak out.
The two neighbors upstairs are two whores.
Hey, leave the phone.
Leave the phone.
Well, calm down.
Oh, calm down.
You're punished.
Calm down.
Roberto.
Roberto, it's me, Nuria.
Nuria, but hey, what are you doing here?
I just moved here in front of you.
Come on, what a coincidence.
No, it's not a coincidence.
Hey, how about you?
How about you?
Are you still with that girl you left me with?
What's her name?
Lucía.
That's it, Lucía.
Yes.
You live here, right?
It seems that things are getting serious, right?
Well, man, we've been together for three years.
Look, you've been with me for three years too.
Do you remember that last week going out with the two of us at the same time?
That if Lucía, that if Nuria, that if Lucía and we went out without knowing anything.
But what a cool guy, huh?
Because I'm sure she still doesn't know, right?
Well, I'm leaving, come on.
I had a son.
Oh yeah?
Congratulations.
You and me.
Boy, I wanted to tell you, but since you didn't pick up the phone, look.
His name is Nacho.
From the Mexican restaurant where you left me.
Damn.
Well, it's a shame we don't cut it in Chinese, if not...
His name would be Chop Suey.
But hey, I'm sure...
No, silly, he's my nephew.
Oh, how good, Nuria.
Hey, let's go down the stairs to see if my blood circulates.
Come on, come on, we'll see each other, huh?
Yes, and a lot.
Because you still don't know it, but you still love me.
Don't worry, huh?
I'm going to open your eyes.
Bye.
These ladies are crazy.
Now they've been given by these poor girls up here.
To know what they'll talk about us.
I'm sure they'll see us, they're very stupid.
Yes, I'm not saying you're right, Paloma.
But it's a very serious matter.
An alternate house here in the building, well, no.
Of course, what I don't understand is how there are men who go with these professionals having their wives in their houses.
Me neither, darling.
Oh no, darling, no.
Juan, I'm tired, you always wait until the last minute.
No, it's true, you're right, I haven't set the time, I'm sorry.
You already know that my good time is the snack.
There, whatever you want, whatever you want, my love.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
To what?
To wash my teeth.
Don't be late.
Yes.
You see, give me the casting address.
Hey, what's that? Another ad?
What I want is to make a series, not to advertise ham cooked.
Hello, good morning.
And how much do they pay?
Only 400 euros?
Yes, they always say the same thing, but then things get long and...
But no.
What about the client?
Yes, I've done something with that.
Shut up.
Well, how am I dressed?
Okay, very good, bye.
Good job.
Oh, that's great.
See you later.
Bye.
Juan.
Juan!
What?
We have to talk.
Who was talking to?
With his boyfriend?
Well, Miguel, for God's sake, what a vocabulary.
What a mouth this child has, hey.
Like his father's, because his mother doesn't get out.
But who likes your parents, Fernando?
Because I could put your faces, but if they are a little old...
No, they are not old, put whatever you want.
It's that if I make rice and they are not punctual, it happens to me that we are fatal.
By the way, when are you going to tell him? Because it can give me a headache.
I don't know, Mauri, I haven't thought about it.
Well, think about it, because if you tell him in the middle of dinner and he gets angry, then look, I don't do it anymore.
Leave the subject of dinner with my parents, please.
If they come, what's wrong with you?
I can't breathe.
What do you mean you can't breathe? Don't scare me, Fernando.
Emilio!
What's wrong?
That you can't breathe.
Really, you call me for everything, huh?
Let me, let me for a moment.
You are very white, you look like a capper, right?
But you are soaked today and your pulse is going to a thousand.
Oh my God, it's going away.
Emilio, please call an ambulance.
No, no, don't worry, I think it's over.
But what do you say?
I am very apprehensive, I can't see blood.
But if there is no blood.
Yes, but if I fall, yes.
I'm better now.
Really, huh?
I don't know what happened to me.
What happened to me?
Don't worry, don't worry.
Let's go get it.
Yes.
Nothing happened.
Okay.
Come on.
Since nothing has happened, it's been a while that the two bastards have made me pass this.
I've been in bed for a while to see if this happens to me a little.
Oh my God.
The bastards.
Don't turn him around anymore.
It has been an anxiety attack.
Yeah, but lately I have a lot of work.
No, it's not because of that.
It's because of dinner with your parents.
Fernando, you are not prepared to tell him.
I want you to leave the closet, but I live.
Well, you'll tell him later.
If I don't tell him, we have a problem.
Well, but I can handle it, and that's it.
I told them that I live with my girlfriend.
Yes, we have a problem.
But why?
Leave it.
Who are you going to tell him to?
Forget it, forget it.
Well, tell them that he has had to go on a trip.
That's it.
No.
No, if it is that he has already gone on a trip.
And he has made communion with his niece.
And his sister has married.
And he has done the elprosuction.
His grandfather has died.
And it is that no more things can happen to him.
He looks like the protagonist of a snake.
Well, then what do I do?
I put on a wig and some heels.
Maybe without heels.
This is the typical moment that would strangle you.
But if I'm doing yoga, it's supposed to be for something.
Hey, I say.
At a given moment.
Oh yes, I can say it.
Yes, yes.
As the thing that ...
This girl, Alicia, the neighbor.
If we ask her for a favor.
Maybe I could make her go through my girlfriend.
Yes, but it's just the time my parents are.
How do you see it?
Very well.
A moment ago you were going to introduce your parents to your homosexual boyfriend.
And now it turns out that the homosexual of my boyfriend has a girlfriend because he has told his parents that he is heterosexual.
Precious.
But only for a while.
And what do I do that little while?
I go to jail with the rabbit.
You were not going to go to the movies?
Besides, you haven't asked Alicia yet.
Maybe she doesn't want to.
Or she can't.
Of course, I loved it.
But why do you have to tell your parents that you have a girlfriend?
Well, because it gets very heavy.
You know, if I'm very old, if the grandchildren, that I get angry.
Alicia, I've invited you.
Well then, what time tomorrow?
Well, I don't know, at nine.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey, how do I look dressed?
Well, I don't know, so you can get an idea.
You work at the buffet.
I'm a waitress.
No, lawyer.
And put on something elegant and a little classic.
You don't have that.
Don't worry, I can leave you whatever you want.
Get on, get on.
The first one has been up for a while.
But they are not gay.
And I don't know if this is a shame.
It's true, here the only ones who don't wet are us.
Hey, thank you very much.
You don't know how well this comes to me.
You're welcome, man, we're scared.
See you tomorrow.
Good morning.
It's not long, is it?
The normal.
He's going to introduce me to his parents.
He's going to introduce you to his parents because he doesn't dare to tell them he's gay.
But why are you so envious?
That this guy is gay?
What's up?
He's gay and he'll be gay forever.
I don't know what's wrong with that, that the one who goes, doesn't come back.
That's true.
Hey.
Hi, honey.
Hi.
This is Nuria, the new neighbor in front.
Nice to meet you.
I was telling Lucia that you have a beautiful house.
Green is my favorite color.
Look.
Hey, weren't we going to the movies?
Yes.
Do you want to come with us?
No, no, I only have two tickets.
Don't worry, we're going to see each other a lot.
You envy me.
It's been a long time since I've had a boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
But I think we're going to come back, because we were a very good couple.
If he's left it, it's because of something, isn't it?
Or not, people make mistakes and maybe he's sorry.
Maybe yes or maybe no, we don't know.
This is talking for talking, if it's not going to ...
He's dating someone else now, but I don't think he's happy.
Sure, I'm sure he still loves you.
No, I don't see it that way.
You're giving advice without knowing.
Love ends and it ends.
No, it doesn't end, Roberto.
Well, if you think you have a solution, you go for it.
I see that as a burden.
And we're going to be late for the movies.
Come on.
Well, couple, I'll leave you.
Well, you calm down.
You'll see how everything is fixed.
And you know, if you want anything, ask me for it.
I'll tell you the same thing, I love sharing.
See you later.
Sorry.
Well, that's good, right?
At least we have nice neighbors in front of us.
Lucia, you get into anyone's house.
The least thought of day we're going to have a taste.
Let's see, what have you talked about?
Well, I don't know, a little bit of everything.
Can you tell me what's wrong with you?
No, no, no, that people are so nice to me, it gives me a bad feeling.
Look, look at the clown from McDonald's.
I think you're getting paranoid here with the whole neighborhood.
Well, I'm going to get my shoes and if you want we go to the movies.
Yes.
I'm going to go to the movies.
Did I have a reason or did I not have a reason?
Yes, madam, you were right.
But hey, have you all gone crazy?
Are you really serious?
Hey, because you haven't heard what Juan and I have heard.
Without cutting, huh? And in front of the child.
400 euros they charge for service.
Fuck, that's what I would charge for pension.
And what I put on the PlayStation when you play.
This neighborhood is getting lost.
Armando, we have to get on all together.
Why? Do you make group discounts? Sure.
No, no, man, not to talk to them.
But let's see what you have done to make them do what they want.
You're getting hooked, like you're making money.
Juan.
By the way, can you show me all this you're saying?
This afternoon at eight, Belén has a client.
But who are you? The secretary?
Well, they have a client, so what?
If the only place from where you could see something is from the floor of the new ones.
They are not.
They are not and they are minus ten.
We are going to get lost.
Hey, Emilio did not have a key to this floor?
Emilio.
Emilio. Yes.
What are you doing?
I was trying to remember a phone number, but it does not come to me.
We need the key to the third floor.
For what? For the ...
Because yes.
But Mr. Cuesta, I can not do this.
I, as the doorman of this farm, have a responsibility with all the neighbors.
When a neighbor gives me his key, for me that is sacred.
We want the girls in the third floor to see that they are prostitutes.
Upstairs.
Wait, wait a moment.
And if I go back to the new ones?
And if someone stays watching?
Very good idea. Stay.
No, then I can not lose it.
Well, you can stand.
Come on, bring the keys here, man, and let's go upstairs.
Come on.
If you see Roberto and Lucia reappear, call me ... call me ...
But how am I going to call you if this is your phone?
No, my wife's.
So this is your wife's phone?
No, this is mine and you call me this other.
If you see them reappear, you give the one and the yes, the green.
So one yes and green.
No, yes and green is the same.
And then when?
The yes, they will come before they know.
Hello, good afternoon.
Hello.
No, no, no, no, no, no, get up, get up.
You charge 400 euros and receive a chandelier.
It's that the chandelier thing now takes a lot.
Damn, how nice they have left this. Menta mandarin.
It's a good idea.
So I painted the gate.
Hey, turn off the light.
And take that yesterday I did not pay you.
Take two.
Wait, let's see if I have the change.
Let's see.
No, this, this, this.
This and this.
Come on.
Well nothing, with love.
Calm down.
Life, life, life, what are we doing here?
Tell me.
No, Juan is not, I am a neighbor.
It's that he left me his phone.
Who is calling me?
Your mother?
Hello.
Do you like this sun?
No, no, no, no.
What a joy, madam.
We thought you had died.
How you were delicate there.
It's been a long time since we saw you around here.
Oh, madam, I have to hang up.
One, Jesse Verde.
Introduce pin.
Pin.
Mr. Cuesta.
Oh, another 400 euros.
These girls in three months they put on a Marbella vest.
400 euros, charge Belén.
Yes.
How the prices have been put, eh, chipote with the euro.
Well, what do you want me to tell you?
I see it very clearly.
Well, maybe he is a friend and he owed him money.
Let's see, this is a decent building and I will not allow moral perversion and the collapse of the house.
One of the values that with so much effort we inculcate our children.
Okay.
Now, having said this, I must add that we do not have any conclusive evidence.
I think that perhaps some of us, if it were to be done by client, could prove it.
You do not eh, Juan.
You do not.
Go put together, surely he is used to these things.
My son does not go to those places.
Well, someone has to go.
If I have to make the effort, I make the effort.
But this pays me for the community.
And above we will fall into a stream.
Happy birthday, happy birthday, I wish you a happy birthday.
Happy birthday of whom?
Can you know what all these people do in my house?
Eh?
Yes, tell me.
They are going up, they are going up.
If it is Vicenta, tell her that it is no longer necessary that the cake is uploaded.
No, no, we already have a good party here.
Natalia, I'm going to throw the garbage and look at the photos.
What are you telling me?
Tell the mother that she is in the bathroom.
I do not talk to her.
Well, write her a note.
Now I come.
Another one that goes up.
Mom, separate the mirilla that the brand is going to leave you.
Of course, and how are you going to throw them if it is also a client?
Juan too.
Come on, the president seemed silly to me.
Normal, married to that.
Of course.
Hello.
Hello, are you busy?
No, I was watching the TV.
This is a bit violent, but could you give me a few minutes?
Yes, yes, of course, come in, come in.
What's wrong with you? Are you feeling bad?
No, nothing, a bad posture.
Ah, what do I do?
I sit down?
Yes, of course, sit down.
Why? I'm not used to these things.
Well, I actually just want to talk.
Talk?
No, it's that I have a problem in bed with my wife.
Ah, well, it's ...
You have a lot of experience in men.
Well, Alicia, I'm more theoretical.
What is the best posture for the woman to reach orgasm?
Well, look, good question.
I think it's a matter of trying.
You recommend me to change.
Yes, but come on, I think this is all with whom, with the time.
You have to talk to your wife, right?
With Paloma? No, I don't prefer to talk to you.
Ah.
Hey, and the point G?
What's wrong with him?
No, where is it? Because there is no way.
Well, I think it's in the head.
Of course, that's why he goes to the hairdresser so much.
No, man, no, it's psychological.
It's that I've read that men also have it.
Well, yes, but you wouldn't like it where?
Well, I have to go. I'm very comfortable, but I don't want Paloma to suspect anything.
Well, it's been very interesting.
It's true what they say about you, you know how to listen to a man.
But, but ...
Please, because I can't afford it anymore, you've won it.
What? It's been a pleasure.
Thanks.
Uh. Hello.
Good night. Good night.
Goodbye. Bye.
And here the president of the community.
Well, he has come, he has told me that he had problems in bed with his wife, he has given me 100 euros and he has not left the bag in the garbage.
How do you interpret it?
Well, I don't know, it's a bit weird, right?
Yes.
I don't know.
Hey.
Damn, Nuria, but how did you get in here?
Are your keys in the door?
Hey, please leave right now. Lucia can come at any time.
I don't think she'll come.
What have you done to her?
Nothing. But Lucia won't be back in an hour.
Hey, don't put it here.
Let's see, what do you want me to do?
Ask for forgiveness?
Come on, okay, I ask for forgiveness.
No, give me a kiss.
Come on, man, give me a kiss and we forget everything.
Come on.
That's it.
No, not enough.
Hey, come on, this is not funny, go.
Oh no? Well, I'm scared.
Oh, by the way, you don't know what I've done.
What?
I've put some of my clothes in Lucia's drawer.
I'm sure you'll recognize her right away.
The question is, will you recognize her?
Oh no.
This one sounds good to me, this one too.
I gave this one to her.
This one doesn't sound good to me.
This one doesn't sound good to me either.
It has a lot of clothes, but why does it have so many?
Hello.
Hey, what's up?
What are you doing?
Well, ordering the drawers, Lucia, they're very messy.
When you live with someone, you have to respect a series of rules, you know?
Damn, we don't have an assistant.
Okay, okay, okay, thank you very much.
Well, when you finish ordering mine, order yours.
Yes, of course, yes, yes.
That's not fixed.
It's not fixed.
Of the many things that come to mind in this situation, the one that comes to mind the most, but from afar, yes.
I prepared dinner and your girlfriend is the one who covers for Gloria.
Well, if you want we can go back in time.
Come on, go back in time.
No, no, it's a mess.
My parents will be on their way.
I can't with your world, Fernando, I can't.
It's eight o'clock.
I think it's a good time.
For what?
Well, for you to go preparing to go to the movies, right?
No, I stay in the room, reading.
When my mother wants to see the bedroom, I tell her what you are.
A stuffed animal.
If the cats are not allergic, tell her you have stress.
I don't leave you here alone with the one above, not even a little bit.
But what happens?
Don't you trust me?
Not you, and less of her.
Look, the girlfriend.
Don't get too close to her, she's doing us a favor.
I'm close, but if she hears the perfect ad, I'll lower the trailer.
Same.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Ali Macbeth, the lawyer.
How are you?
Fuck, you are very good.
I brought you some pictures for the living room.
And then I brought you this little one for your wallet.
Then if you want you can keep it.
I also brought clothes for your wardrobe.
Here, the shoes to be at home.
Some notes for the fridge.
A box of tampons for the bathroom.
And some passions and official magazine.
Very professional.
I like to prepare myself.
Listen, we met three years ago.
I was your boss and you fell in love with me.
Two months later we were living together.
We want to get married but we can't find a place.
We want to have two children, Ariadna and Gael.
And we like yoga a lot.
Formenting in the documentary of whales, what do you think?
Good.
What are your parents' names?
Enrique and Monse.
Hey, we should kiss sometime, right?
What was that?
Felix. The cat.
Ah, we have a cat.
Three.
Oh, how cute, I put it on the table.
Do you want me to help you find a movie?
No, thank you very much.
Hello.
Hi.
What? Did you find my balls?
Yes, I found them and threw them away.
Really?
Well, it has a lot of merit because I didn't put any.
What are you looking at?
Hey, is there any chance, even if it's small, that you leave me alone once?
Yes, lie down with me.
Okay.
And any easier?
Yes, I can also tell Lucia that you were going out with both at the same time and see how she feels.
Hey, don't do that to me, please, I'm very in love.
I was also very in love three years ago.
Look, you have 24 hours to decide.
Here you have my number.
Bye.
What do you mean, bye? And is the movie taking?
It can take whatever you want. Have you seen how it is?
Yes, like a goat.
So maybe I have a chance.
Well, you're going to make a good couple, look.
Where are you going? The 21 is here.
Excuse me, the floor of Fernando and his girlfriend?
Fernando and his girlfriend, how good, the first B.
Thank you.
See you later.
Damn, it's late, I'm going to fix it.
Honey, your parents.
Pagasus.
Hello, mom.
Son.
And, have you gotten fat?
Fuck, what it has cost us in the movie, we have to go to the cinema.
Hey, and in the portal there is a junkie?
No, it's the doorman.
Son, what a neighborhood.
Well, I'm going to introduce you to Lorena, my girlfriend.
Hello.
Very pretty.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Do you want to drink something?
Me, a white wine and my husband a Jerez.
Well.
Hey, but what color have you painted this?
This is gray.
I like it, the living room is wide.
And the kitchen?
This is the kitchen.
Ah, very modern, so everything together.
And that?
It's a singer, mom.
Ah, of course, Camilo Sexto.
Fernando, love, where have you left the glasses?
You have them in front of you, my life.
Well, what have you prepared for dinner?
Dinner?
What is there for dinner?
Well, this is a puree like potato.
And this is another meat with sauce.
Bichissuá and duck's blood with tangerine and mango.
Useless.
That.
It's very modest.
How long will this one take? What will he be doing?
Today.
How beautiful, what a diva.
Very handsome, Emilio.
Now you will fulfill.
But I like this uniform more.
Here, Emilio, 400 euros from the funds reserved for the community.
Melio, tell him not to do a invoice, we almost saved ourselves the same.
Hey, and you, do something to see if they give us a discount for being neighbors.
Wait a minute, but the money does not have to be spent.
No, because when he offers it to the girls and they accept, we can throw them away.
But if Emilio does not have to do anything.
No, Mrs. Paloma, things are either done well or not done.
There must be conclusive evidence.
If you do not get to wear the dress, who believes it is Monica Lewinsky's?
That's right.
Come on, and now all up.
Emilio, you first, gentleman, please.
Come on, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Come on, yes, yes, yes.
There goes that macho, that macho.
Come on, come on.
Look, Lucia, this is what there is.
I went out with the two of them for a week.
And what? I did not tell you not to hurt yourself.
What, you do not like it?
Well, you'll have to learn to live with it.
What do you want me to tell you?
It kills me, it kills me, son.
I can not tell you or fuck.
Hello, honey.
Lucia. What?
The neighbor is crazy.
Which of them? Because we have to choose.
Nuria, the one in front is like a fucking goat.
She is harassing me.
Look, Roberto, as soon as a woman looks at you,
you think she wants to sleep with you.
No, no, no, no, she is obsessed.
She has moved here for me.
Honey, I love you very much.
But you are not Brad Pitt.
No, of course not.
I am Michael Douglas and Jean-Claude Claus in Fatal Attraction.
You know what I'm telling you? Have you seen it?
The thing with the knives.
Yes.
But she was saying out there that she was my girlfriend.
Roberto, look, you spend many hours at home drawing.
And maybe the smell of the markers is crazy.
Don't you believe me?
Well, no.
Okay, I'm going to call her.
You'll see how she presents herself right now.
You don't know this bitch.
Fuck, I'm nervous.
Let the time that doesn't ...
Hello.
What are you wearing?
Sorry, is Alicia there?
Well, no, she was not down first.
Do a favor to Fernando.
Well, then I'll be back for another moment.
I'm here.
What do you want, Emilio?
Can I stop by for a while and chat a little?
Another?
Well, what's wrong with you all?
Well, we are alone, Belén.
Come on, come on.
But for a while, huh?
I'm very busy.
Of course, of course.
It's just that people are no longer for movies.
Well, what do we do?
Well, I don't know, Emilio.
You will tell me.
Well, I don't know, get me a beer or something.
To get me loose a little.
Are you also going to give me 100 euros?
I have 200 euros.
For you.
I don't understand anything.
But I'm going to get drunk.
This is also good, damn it.
Yes.
But this is delicious, Lorena.
Well, my hand is a little bit dirty with the salt.
Be careful if you give me your hand too.
How about in Mallorca?
Very good.
Let's see when you come to see us.
When you want, we are delighted.
What's wrong with those cats?
There is an oncelo.
Well, Lorena, what case are you in now?
Fernando told me that you have specialized in ecological crimes.
It's just that my father is also a lawyer.
Ah, how good.
Ecological crimes.
Well, it's a case that is very curious.
Because it comes from a zookeeper who was cleaning in the nutrient tank.
And he slipped and fell.
With such bad luck that he put his foot in the panda bear cage.
And he bit him.
He tore his three fingers, come on, he ate them.
But pandas don't eat bamboo.
Yes, yes, but he wore bamboo on his shoe.
And he also gave himself a nail polish to separate the wounds from the nails.
And the panda bear got intoxicated and died.
So the caretaker ate the nails of the feet.
It's just that he had previously been a contortionist in the Cirque du Soleil.
But hey, the case is that since the panda bear is a protected species,
the zoo has sued the caretaker.
And the caretaker has sued the nail polish brand
for not putting it on the prospect, which is lethal for panda bears.
It's a very complicated case.
Have you read it in the newspaper?
No.
Well, I'm going to get dessert.
Fernando, he's a great lawyer.
He doesn't understand anything at all.
I'll drink that beer from that kid,
otherwise I'll have to go to hell.
What are you doing?
You're degenerate.
You're going to pay me for 200 euros.
What am I going to do to you?
What have you believed?
What is this?
Fernando, what have you believed?
What kind of treatment is this for a client?
What client?
Get out of here!
You're calling me a whore, Emilio.
I'm not a whore.
What am I going to do?
Get out of my house!
You're not whores.
What do you mean?
Emilio, please, shut up.
I've already called the police.
What have you done?
What do you want us to do?
Nothing happens.
I'm going to call the police.
It's here.
Hide and listen.
Wait.
Take this just in case.
Don't you think you're exaggerating?
No, this is a movie.
Yes, you're right.
Hello, you called me, right?
Yes, come in.
Yes, we're going to do it.
What?
What do you mean?
Take off your clothes.
Roberto, it's not funny.
You have a girlfriend.
Don't play hard to get with me.
Get out of my pants.
What's wrong?
You have problems with Lucia?
No, I have problems with you.
You're scaring me.
I'd better go.
Give me a kiss right now.
I don't want to.
You're not going to kiss me.
Leave me alone.
I don't know.
She's been moving for a month.
I'm not crazy.
She's the only crazy one here.
What?
We've been dating for three years.
You're lying.
What do you mean?
I was dating both of them and I decided to marry her.
Well, it wasn't so hard to tell your girlfriend.
I'm sorry, Lucia, but I was so bad when she left me.
I had to get revenge.
Be happy.
Don't worry.
I'm going to my house tomorrow.
I have a beautiful duplex in the centre.
Bye.
I'm not telling you.
No, no.
You're not mad, are you?
No, not at all.
Do you want to go to the knife?
You gave him 200 euros.
We're all going to see it at the same time.
Don't tell anyone we didn't find out.
Can you be more polite to the agent?
For example, who's this person?
Me? The porter.
Is he usually going naked in the building?
No.
Juan Cuesta, the mayor of the community.
I can explain everything in two words.
No, don't get me wrong.
These people who don't have a life of their own,
they make up for it.
And they've been told that my flatmate and I are prostitutes.
But you have proof of that.
Do you want to file a complaint?
Of course.
A complaint doesn't come from the court.
Please, come with me to the police station.
It was a mistake, sir.
We know it because this lady told us.
There were men going up and down.
These two are two gulfs.
I'm telling you, I'm your housekeeper.
Can you show me the rent contract?
What contract? We haven't been hired yet.
Let's see.
You come with us too.
We'll file a complaint.
You're arresting me?
Of course, mom. Why are you calling them?
We're getting things out of Kiccio.
This is just a misunderstanding.
You shut up.
Yesterday you came to my house and offered me 100 euros.
You too, Mr. Cuesta.
What is this girl saying?
I swear I never had the slightest physical contact with her.
That's what Clinton said.
I'm about to cry.
Get in the car.
Don't tell the kids anything.
This is a regrettable mistake.
My husband?
We should have brought the van.
My husband is coming to dinner.
I don't know, ma'am.
I'll make him something cold.
Juan, calm down.
Calm down, woman.
Juan!
You'll be here tomorrow, woman.
You'll be here tomorrow.
It's our fault.
You can't blame anyone without evidence.
What do you mean?
That happens every day at the conference and nothing ever happens.
That's true.
What am I going to do tonight? I can't sleep without my husband.
You can sleep with me at the door, Mrs. Paloma.
How can I sleep with you at the door?
My husband will kill me.
Fernando, this girl is perfect.
She's pretty, smart and smart.
She has a good job and she likes you.
She doesn't lack anything.
Yes, a penis.
I'm delighted.
We have to come more often.
Of course, for the wedding.
You're getting married?
But, son, why didn't you tell me anything?
Because we wanted it to be a surprise.
What a joy.
Because I don't disapprove of this situation, but...
Yes, she disapproves.
She has given me a lot of travel.
But it's much nicer to be married.
Where are you going to stop?
Excuse me for a moment. I'll be right back.
Hey, if you want, I can look for my dress.
Maybe it's worth it.
Because I had more or less your body.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
How are you?
Bad. I don't know what I'm doing here.
I look like a stressor.
Don't worry, everything is going very well.
My parents are delighted.
And only your parents.
Come on, give me a kiss.
Excuse me.
Damn it.
Aren't you going to the bathroom, Enrique?
No, no, no. I'm waiting for the hotel.
Are you okay?
Regular. Regular.
I don't usually pee, you know?
Do you want to take a nap?
No. No, no.
Well, look, we better go.
Do you want me to call you?
No, no. We better go for a walk.
I told you I was wearing heels.
Dad, are you sure you're okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
It's been a wedding.
Your father's nerves are going to his stomach.
Well, we'll see you later.
It's been a pleasure, daughter.
Enrique, wait for me.
What a pity, right?
With how well we were having fun.
Well, I don't know why you had to lie to me.
Because I thought you were going to take it badly.
I don't know, you're dating someone else at the beginning of our relationship.
I had a boyfriend when I met you.
Really?
Well, yes. It's normal not to be clear at first, right?
It was also very difficult for me to decide.
How much?
You two are very different.
Well, I don't know, a month.
A month? Mine was a week.
Who was it?
What are you talking about? You don't know him.
Well, if you don't know him.
No, it wouldn't be Carlos.
Oh, well, if you know him.
How do you know him?
But why didn't you tell me?
A draw.
Well, it's my fault.
I should have told him directly.
Let's see how I explain this now.
Calm down Fernando, look at the positive side.
Which one?
I don't know, I'm looking for it.
Mauri, my mother can give you something when she finds out about this.
Call your father and tell him to tell him on the plane.
So the poor woman can get oxygen.
Thanks.
But... Hello.
Fernando, your father.
Dad.
Can I come in for a moment?
Yes, I have to go shopping.
Stay, stay.
I wanted to talk to you.
You're gay, right?
Yes.
Me too.
And me?
But dad...
I've been attracted to men for years.
But I'm married and I have a family.
But I want you to know that I support you and I understand you.
Well...
One moment.
And mom knows something about this?
Are you crazy or what?
And now how do I explain it? Because come on.
It's your problem, don't mess with me.
I'm going to run away because I'm going to miss the plane.
And if you go for Palma,
you know that I act on Thursdays at 11 and 1 in the Cabaret Las Vegas.
My name is Delito.
Bye.
I don't introduce you to my parents.
They're going to look like a lot of shit.
Delito?
You're a man of your word, Delito.
Paco!
Pacito!
Look!
Look at this dog I bought.
How much did it cost?
400 euros.
It's a nice job.
It's cool that you like it.
But you have meat to carry this.
But if you don't need meat, close that and get on the plane.
Come on.
Nobody is going to get in.
You have 125 horsepower per cubic meter.
Come on, let's go.